I also can add up reference images, right?
So a reference image is something
that we want to include in the generated image.
So for example, a logo or something like that, right?
Or we can add a reference image and our prompt
can be all about editing the very image that we gave it, right?
So this is how we can edit our images with photorei.
It's very easy.
You just upload your image over here.
So it can be an image of you, for example, right?
Or an image containing you and a crowd of people.
And then you explain to it that, for example,
you want all everybody to be blurred, you know?
Or you want everybody to be removed from the image, right?
Or any kind of edit that you want to add to that very image.
And by clicking generate, you'll be able to get the very image
that you gave it as a reference image just
with the edit additions, you know, and with the changes
that you wanted to make.
And that's pretty much all.
I don't want to add any kind of reference images for now.